Guide to the Shaun Maloney Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Shaun Maloney papers, 1932-2000; 5255-001; 35.08 cu. ft. (37 units); 261 sound cassette tapes; 10 videocassettes (VHS); 1 sound tape reel; 7 sound cassette tapes (microcassettes)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union. Local 19
    - Subject Series
      - Earnings "A", 1973 (Box-folder 20/53)
      - Elwell, Lee Port of Seattle, 1974 (Box-folder 20/54)
      - Engelhard Exhaust Purifier, Monoxide Control, Bulls, etc., n.d. (Box-folder 20/55)
      - Equipment, 1972 (Box-folder 20/56)
      - Extended Shifts, Gear Violation, 1961-1964, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 20/57-58)
      - Federal Harbor Workers Comp., n.d. (Box-folder 20/59)
      - File on Steadies Rule 4, Kagel Awards History & Complaints by C/O, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 20/60-61)
      - Filipino Seamen, SS Silvertone, 1972 (Box-folder 20/62)
      - Gang Quotas P.S. Area CLRC #24, 1963, 1975 (Box-folder 21/1)
      - Hansford, Joe Geo. Bush, 1972 (Box-folder 21/2)
      - Harbor Workers Compensation Act 1/25/73, 1973 (Box-folder 21/3)
      - Holiday Knockoff Xmas - New Years, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 21/4)
      - Honda Freight Sheets, 1971 (Box-folder 21/5)
      - Howard Cooper Wagner Front Grabs, n.d. (Box-folder 21/6)
      - Hyster, Clark, Lift Trucks, Foss Alaska Line, n.d. (Box-folder 21/7)
      - ILA CONASA New York Contract, 1972 (Box-folder 21/8)
      - ILA Contracts, 1972 (Box-folder 21/9)
      - ILA Data, 1973 (Box-folder 21/10)
      - ILWU - PMA Pension Plan, 1968 (Box-folder 21/11)
      - Industrial Hygienists and Sounds (Box-folder 21/12)
      - July 4th Holiday Pay, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 21/13)
      - Labor for Peace, 1972 (Box-folder 21/14)
      - Line Service, 1966, 1973 (Box-folder 21/15-17)
      - Line Service - Line Accounts, 1972 (Box-folder 21/18)
      - Line Service - Line Gang Earnings, 1967, 1971-1973, n.d. (Box-folder 21/19)
      - Line Service - Lines & Gear Contracts, 1964, 1971-1972, n.d. (Box-folder 21/20)
      - Line Service - Lineman's Agreement, 1966, 1972 (Box-folder 21/21)
      - Line Service - Local 10 Lines, Misc., 1972, n.d. (Box-folder 21/22)
      - Local 10, 1974 (Box-folder 21/23)
      - Local 40, 1975 (Box-folder 21/24)
      - Log Exports, 1973 (Box-folder 21/25)
      - Love Award, 1973 (Box-folder 21/26)
      - Manpower Survey, 1975 (Box-folder 21/27)
      - Matson Monster, n.d. (Box-folder 21/28)
      - Miscellaneous Items for LRC, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 21/29)
      - NASA, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 21/30)
      - NLRB 2nd Case Contract - Tariff, 1970 (Box-folder 21/31)
      - Noise - Pressman's Brief, 1972 (Box-folder 21/32)
      - Occupational Health and Safety Act of 1970 (Box-folder 21/33)
      - Original Arbitrators Award (Appendix #11), 1934 (Box-folder 21/34)
      - OSHA - Cap Skolman, 1972 (Box-folder 21/35)
      - OSHA Portland, 1974 (Box-folder 21/36)
      - Out Port Travel, n.d. (Box-folder 21/37)
      - Penalties - Background and Arbitration, 1973 (Box-folder 21/38)
      - Pension, H & W, Dental, etc., 1972 (Box-folder 21/39)
      - PMA Offer - Vote 12, 1971 (Box-folder 21/40)
      - Pool Hours, 1970 (Box-folder 21/41)
      - Portland Arbitration - Labor Day, 1974 (Box-folder 21/42)
      - Portland Gear Locker Agreement, 1973 (Box-folder 21/43)
      - Portland Toyota - Rivergate, Scope of Work, 1972 (Box-folder 21/44)
      - Port of Seattle, Jan. 1, 1973 (Box-folder 21/45)
      - Ralph Parsons Company, 1974 (Box-folder 21/46)
      - Rank & File Committee, 1971 (Box-folder 21/47)
      - Rausch - Glasses, 1972 (Box-folder 21/48)
      - R.I.S. Shortage, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 21/49)
      - Runaway Container Freight Sta. Portland, 1975 (Box-folder 21/50)
      - San Francisco, Oct. 25, 1972 (Box-folder 21/51)
      - Seattle King County Plan Proposal #2, 1974 (Box-folder 21/52)
      - Seattle Port Rules, Other Than in Port Working and Dispatcher Rules, 1967 (Box-folder 21/53)
      - Seattle Stevedore SS Hoegh Miranda, 1972 (Box-folder 21/54)
      - Senate Bill 1033 re: Log Exports, 1973 (Box-folder 21/55)
      - Shrink Pack Beef, 1973 (Box-folder 21/56)
      - Shrink Pack, State Lines, 1975 (Box-folder 21/57)
      - Steady Crane Operators, 1972 (Box-folder 21/58)
      - Steady Men - 9.43 & Steady Men Mills, 1973 (Box-folder 21/59)
      - Steady Men - Kagel on Steady Men, 1972 (Box-folder 21/60)
      - Steady Men File, May 1974 (Box-folder 21/61-62)
      - Strict Products Liability Streatch v. Associated Container Transp. Ltd., 1975 (Box-folder 21/63)
      - Strike Committee, 1972 (Box-folder 21/64)
      - Strike Votes, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 21/65)
      - T. 143 SS San Francisco, 1968-1969, 1974 (Box-folder 21/66)
      - Terminal 102 Headmarks v. Sub-Marks, Mar. 18, 1975 (Box-folder 21/67)
      - T-Letter #108, 113, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 21/68)
      - T-Mannings, 1969 (Box-folder 21/69)
      - Tote, 1975 (Box-folder 21/70)
      - Travel, 1963, 1973 (Box-folder 21/71)
      - U.S. Customs, n.d. (Box-folder 21/72)
      - Vacation, Pension Qualifications, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 21/73)
      - Vining, Dave Superintendent, Port of Seattle - Docks, Whse., 1974 (Box-folder 21/74)
      - Wage Control - Auburn College, 1972 (Box-folder 21/75)
      - Wage Surveys, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 21/76)
      - Walden, T., 1971-1972 (Box-folder 21/77)
      - Washington District Annual Longshore Payrolls (Box-folder 21/78)
      - Welfare & Retirement Plans, 1966, n.d. (Box-folder 21/79)
      - Workmen's Compensation, 1972 (Box-folder 21/80)
      - World Container Ports, 1973 (Box-folder 21/81)
    - Speeches and Writings
      - Remarks at ILWU Convention, 1971 (Box-folder 21/82)
      - KIRO, 1972 (Box-folder 21/83)
      - Drafts, n.d. (Box-folder 21/84-85)
    - Speeches and Writings of Others
      - Bridges, Harry, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 21/86)
      - ILWU Local 19, 1971, n.d. (Box-folder 21/87)
      - ILWU Local 40, 1975 (Box-folder 21/88)
      - Mills, Herb, n.d. (Box-folder 21/89)
      - Nelson, Burt, 1971 (Box-folder 21/90)
      - Miscellaneous, 1940, 1966, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 21/91)
    - Reports
      - Accident, 1972 (Box-folder 22/1)
      - Annual Report - Legal Committee, Pacific Coast Association of Port Authority, 1975 (Box-folder 22/2)
      - Coast Contract Negotiations, n.d. (Box-folder 22/3)
      - Coast Labor Relations Committee, 1974, n.d. (Box-folder 22/4-5)
      - Copier Costs, 1972 (Box-folder 22/6)
      - N.T. Nemetz, 1972 (Box-folder 22/7)
      - PMA Annual Report, 1974 (Box-folder 22/8)
      - Port of Butte, n.d. (Box-folder 22/9)
    - Reports of Others
      - Perry, Hugh J. - Noise Consulting for the Port of Seattle Planning and Research Department, 1975 (Box-folder 22/10)
      - Miscellaneous, 1971-1975, 1994, n.d. (Box-folder 22/11-13)
    - Agreements
      - ILWU & PMA, 1972 (Box-folder 22/14)
      - ILWU Local 19/Port of Seattle, 1972, n.d. (Box-folder 22/15)
      - Miscellaneous, 1969-1970, 1975 (Box-folder 22/16-17)
    - Case Files
      - Ajay Enterprises, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 22/18)
      - NLRB v. Mechanists Local 289 I.A.M., Sept. 6, 1975 (Box-folder 22/19)
      - NLRB International Container Service Inc. v. Local 19, 1972 (Box-folder 22/20)
      - NLRB Seattle-Rothschild Stevedoring Co. v. Local 19, 1971 (Box-folder 22/21)
    - Affidavits-Peeler, n.d. (Box-folder 22/22)
    - Legal Documents, 1971 (Box-folder 22/23)
    - Court Papers
      - ILWU - Canadian Area BC Workers Comp. Board, 1973 (Box-folder 22/24)
      - ILWU Local 19 & Int'l Container Sve. (NLRB), 1971 (Box-folder 22/25)
      - ILWU Local 19 & Machinists 289 (NLRB), 1975 (Box-folder 22/26)
      - Labor Board, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 22/27)
      - NLRB v. Fluor Engineers & Construction, 1974 (Box-folder 22/28)
      - NLRB v. ILWU Local 50, 1974 (Box-folder 22/29)
      - NLRB v. Sternoff Metals, 1974 (Box-folder 22/30)
      - PMA v. ILWU Local 19, 1972 (Box-folder 22/31)
      - PMA v. ILWU Local 19 (First Action), 1972 (Box-folder 22/32)
      - PMA v. ILWU Local 19 (Second & Later Actions), 1972 (Box-folder 22/33)
      - Port of Seattle v. PMA, 1974 (Box-folder 22/34)
      - Roth & ILWU Local 19 (NLRB), 1972 (Box-folder 22/35)
      - Subpoena, 1967, 1974 (Box-folder 22/36)
      - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box-folder 22/37)
    - Legislation, 1971, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 22/38-39)
    - Regulations, 1965-1974 (Box-folder 22/40-41)
    - Resolutions
      - December Caucus, n.d. (Box-folder 22/42)
      - Miscellaneous, 1973, 1975, n.d. (Box-folder 22/43-46)
    - Resolutions of Others
      - State of Washington, 1972 (Box-folder 22/47)
    - Petitions, n.d. (Box-folder 22/48)
    - Negotiations
      - Foss Alaska, 1971 (Box-folder 22/49)
      - Foss Launch & Tug Co., 1971-1973 (Box-folder 22/50)
      - 9.43, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 22/51)
      - W/O Rules, n.d. (Box-folder 22/52)
      - Miscellaneous, 1971-1975, n.d. (Box-folder 22/53-63)
    - Arbitration Decisions
      - Appeal W-8-73, 1973 (Box-folder 22/64)
      - Area Arbitrator, 1969-1977, 1988 (Box-folder 23/1)
      - Car Ships; Hatch Boards; Rigging Ramps; Button Men; Elevators, 1970, 1972, 1974 (Box-folder 23/2)
      - Coast Arbitrator, 1970 (Box-folder 23/3)
      - Container Freight 102, n.d. (Box-folder 23/4)
      - July 5, 1972 (Box-folder 23/5)
      - Love Award, Containers, 1971 (Box-folder 23/6)
      - Love Award - Kagel Opinion; Forrester - Decision re: Eyhres Transfer Co., 1971 (Box-folder 23/7)
      - Rigging; Auto Ramps, 1970, 1974 (Box-folder 23/8)
      - Steady Men, 1971 (Box-folder 23/9)
    - Indices to Arbitration Awards
      - 1934-1960, n.d. (Box-folder 23/10)
      - 1961-1970, n.d. (Box-folder 23/11)
      - 1972-1973, n.d. (Box-folder 23/12)
      - California, 1973, 1974, n.d. (Box-folder 23/13)
      - Oregon Area, 1973, 1974, n.d. (Box-folder 23/14)
      - Washington Area, 1973, 1974, n.d. (Box-folder 23/15)
    - Complaints
      - Crane, 1973 (Box-folder 23/16)
      - S/Land - Shortage Driver Complaints, 1971 (Box-folder 23/17)
    - Employer Complaints
      - Santa Monica, 1972 (Box-folder 23/18)
      - S.S. Blankenstein, 1972 (Box-folder 23/19)
      - Wooding, K., n.d. (Box-folder 23/20)
      - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box-folder 23/21)
    - Grievance Files
      - S.S. Akarita Seattle Stevedore Co. Pier 91 5/6/74, 1974 (Box-folder 23/22)
      - Canada Mail, 1972 (Box-folder 23/23)
    - Claims
      - Union, 1975 (Box-folder 23/24)
      - Union - Shrink Pack; Building 45 States Line; Nor-Pac, 1973 (Box-folder 23/25)
      - Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box-folder 23/26)
    - Referrals - To Joint Coast LRC, 1973, 1994, n.d. (Box-folder 23/27)
    - Elections, 1970-1975; Includes oversized. (Box-folder 23/28)
    - Directories
      - ILWU, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 23/29-31)
      - Labor Organizations, n.d. (Box-folder 23/32)
      - PMA Member Companies, 1968 (Box-folder 23/33)
      - Ships, Agents, Piers, n.d. (Box-folder 23/34)
      - Washington State Cranes & Grain Spouts, 1974 (Box-folder 23/35)
      - Unidentified, n.d. (Box-folder 23/36)
    - Lists, 1973 (Box-folder 23/37)
    - Rosters
      - B-Men 2nd Group (Box-folder 23/38)
      - B-Men Low Earnings, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 23/39)
      - B-Men No Hours, 1973 (Box-folder 23/40)
      - Bull Board, n.d. (Box-folder 23/41)
      - Bull, Deck, Trucker Lists, n.d. (Box-folder 23/42)
      - Bull Lists, 1975 (Box-folder 23/43)
      - Crane Earnings, 1972 (Box-folder 23/44)
      - Crane Operators, 1972 (Box-folder 23/45)
      - Crane Operators - 4th Quarter, 1st Draft of Printout, n.d. (Box-folder 23/46)
      - Crane Operators and Straddle Operators, June 14, 1972 (Box-folder 23/47)
      - Crane Operators Recap, 1973-1974, n.d. (Box-folder 23/48-49)
      - Crane & Straddle Certified Operators, 1972 (Box-folder 23/50)
      - Day & Night, 1973 (Box-folder 23/51)
      - Day - Night - Boards, n.d. (Box-folder 23/52)
      - Deck Lists, 1975, n.d. (Box-folder 23/53)
      - Foreman's Agreement, n.d. (Box-folder 23/54)
      - Gang Lists, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 23/55)
      - ILWU Locals Washington, n.d. (Box-folder 23/56)
      - John Leppa; Crane Straddle Breakdown, n.d. (Box-folder 23/57)
      - Low Earnings A & B, 1971 (Box-folder 23/58)
      - Manpower, 1963, n.d. (Box-folder 23/59)
      - Manpower; Gang Structure, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 23/60)
      - New Members 1/17/74, Jan. 17, 1974 (Box-folder 23/61)
      - Out Port Visitors Tacoma, Everett, 1975 (Box-folder 23/62)
      - Seattle Crane Operators, 1965-1968, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 23/63)
      - Straddle Operators, 1972 (Box-folder 23/64)
      - Unidentified, 1972, 1973-1975, n.d. (Box-folder 23/65-68)
    - Logs
      - Sea Land, 1972 (Box-folder 23/69)
      - Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 23/70-73)
    - Dispatch Records, 1975 (Box-folder 23/74)
    - Schedules
      - 7-Day Dispatch; Dispatcher, Aug. 25, 1974 (Box-folder 23/75)
      - Wage, 1975-1976; n.d. (Box-folder 23/76)
    - Notes
      - Negotiations, 1971 (Box-folder 23/77)
      - Re: Alyeska, 1974 (Box-folder 23/78)
      - Re: Williams Hearing, 1974 (Box-folder 23/79)
      - Miscellaneous, 1971-1975, n.d. (Box-folder 23/80-97)
    - Calendars - Clerks & Foreman, 1972 (Box-folder 24/1)
    - Business Cards, n.d. (Box-folder 24/2-3)
    - Project Descriptions of Others, n.d. (Box-folder 24/4)
    - Photographs, ca. 1972-1973
    - Form Letters, n.d. (Box-folder 24/6)
    - Personnel Files
      - Pension Eligibility, n.d. (Box-folder 24/7)
    - Financial Records
      - Financial Study, Mar. 13-15, 1973 (Box-folder 24/8-9)
      - Miscellaneous, 1972, 1975, n.d. (Box-folder 24/10-13)
    - Financial Reports
      - ILWU-PMA Pension Fund, 1966 (Box-folder 24/14)
      - ILWU - PMA Vesting, Benefit Fund, 1972 (Box-folder 24/15)
      - International Longshoremen's Benevolent Fund, 1975 (Box-folder 24/16)
    - Forms
      - Container Forms PCL Pier 46, n.d. (Box-folder 24/17)
      - Container Forms Pier 18, n.d. (Box-folder 24/18)
    - Surveys, 1971, n.d. (Box-folder 24/19)
    - Bulletins, 1972 (Box-folder 24/20)
    - Newsletters
      - Area Strike Bulletin, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 24/21)
      - BALMA (Bay Area Longshoremen's Memorial Assoc.), 1972-1974 (Box-folder 24/22)
      - ILWU Local 10 Longshore Bulletin, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 24/23)
      - ILWU Local 10 Strike Bulletin, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 24/24)
      - ILWU Local 13 Strike Bulletin, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 24/25)
      - [ILWU] Local 21 Reports, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 24/26)
      - ILWU Washington Report, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 24/27)
      - LRC Bulletin, 1972 (Box-folder 24/28)
      - Seattle, Port of, 1974 (Box-folder 24/29)
      - Strike Bulletin [ILWU Local 19], 1971 (Box-folder 24/30)
      - Miscellaneous, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 24/31)
    - News Releases, 1971 (Box-folder 24/32)
    - News Releases of Others, 1973-1974, 1976 (Box-folder 24/33)
    - Transcripts (of Proceedings)
      - 1971 Caucus (Box-folder 24/34)
      - Biennial Convention, 1971 (Box-folder 24/35)
      - Equalization of Work Opportunities, n.d. (Box-folder 24/36)
      - ILWU v. PMA Arbitration, 1979 (Box-folder 24/37)
      - KIRO Editorial, 1972 (Box-folder 24/38)
      - Mobile Crane Arbitration, 1972 (Box-folder 24/39)
      - PMA v. ILWU Arbitration (Sea-Land Slowdown), 1972 (Box-folder 24/40)
      - PMA v. ILWU Local 19, 1972 (Box-folder 24/41)
      - Seattle Joint Port LRC Discrimination Hearing, 1974 (Box-folder 24/42)
      - Third Caucus re: 10.24, 1966 (Box-folder 24/43)
      - Unidentified, n.d. (Box-folder 24/44)
    - Manuals
      - Payroll, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 24/45-46)
      - Payroll Manual Revisions, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box-folder 24/47)
    - Flyers, n.d. (Box-folder 24/48-50)
    - Publications
      - 1964 Relative Values Studies (Box-folder 24/51)
      - Harry Bridges Testimonial Dinner, 1975 (Box-folder 24/52)
      - Drug Abuse, 1971, n.d. (Box-folder 24/53)
      - Marine Index Bureau Statistical Analysis, 1974 (Box-folder 24/54)
      - Maritime Worker, 1974 (Box-folder 24/55)
      - On the Waterfront, n.d. (Box-folder 24/56)
      - Pacific Longshore Industry 1934-1970 (Box-folder 24/57)
      - People's World, 1975 (Box-folder 24/58)
      - Port News, 1974 (Box-folder 24/59)
      - Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box-folder 24/60)
      - Transport Worker, 1973 (Box-folder 24/61)
      - U.S. Department of Labor, 1956-1967 (Box-folder 24/62)
      - Waterfront Worker, 1974 (Box-folder 24/63)
    - Pamphlets, n.d. (Box-folder 24/64-73)
    - Clippings
      - Fact Articles, 1973 (Box-folder 24/74)
      - Paul Hall; SIU, 1973 (Box-folder 24/75)
      - 1971 Strike, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 24/76)
      - Sea Land, 1972 (Box-folder 24/77)
      - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box-folder 24/78-79)
    - Miscellany
      - Loose Papers, 1970-1975, n.d. (Box-folder 24/80-84 to 25/1-9)
      - Foldered, 1971-1974, n.d. (Box-folder 25/10-31)
      - Miscellaneous Vol. II, 1971 (Box-folder 25/32)
      - Miscellaneous Vol. I, 1972 (Box-folder 25/33)
      - Miscellaneous Vol. II, 1972 (Box-folder 25/34)
    - Ephemera, n.d. (Box-folder 25/35-36)
    - 9.43 and Steady Men Joint Negotiations Subcommittee
      - Negotiations
        - 9.43, 1973 (Box-folder 25/37)
        - Miscellaneous, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 25/38-43)
  - International Longshoremen's And Warehousemen's Union (Post Retirement)
    - Organizational Features, 1994, n.d. (Box-folder 25/44-45)
    - Outgoing Letters of Others
      - American President Lines, 1976-1992, n.d. (Box-folder 25/46)
      - Bridges, Harry, 1937, 1976 (Box-folder 25/47)
      - Delay, Dallas, 1979-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 25/48)
      - Duggan, Robert, 1976-1992 (Box-folder 25/49)
      - Eagle Marine Services, 1981 (Box-folder 25/50)
      - Frazier, Bob, 1994 (Box-folder 25/51)
      - Herman, James, 1977-1990 (Box-folder 25/52)
      - ILWU (International and Coast Committee), 1974-1998 (Box-folder 25/53)
      - ILWU, Alaska Council, 1978, n.d. (Box-folder 25/54)
      - ILWU, Local 10, 1976-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 25/55)
      - ILWU, Local 13, 1976-1997 (Box-folder 25/56)
      - ILWU, Local 19, 1976-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 26/1-3)
      - ILWU, Local 23, 1981, 1998 (Box-folder 26/4)
      - ILWU, Local 34, 1976-1994 (Box-folder 26/5)
      - ILWU, Local 37, 1986 (Box-folder 26/6)
      - ILWU - PMA Benefit Plans, 1978-1997 (Box-folder 26/7)
      - ILWU, Various Locals, 1954, 1976-1998 (Box-folder 26/8)
      - Lindsay, Dennis, 1976, 1987 (Box-folder 26/9)
      - McWilliams, Brian, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 26/10)
      - Moork, Dick, 1976-1984, n.d. (Box-folder 26/11)
      - Munson, John, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 26/12)
      - National Labor Relations Board, 1979-1995 (Box-folder 26/13)
      - Pacific Maritime Association, 1976-1997 (Box-folder 26/14)
      - Seattle. Port, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 26/15)
      - Reinhardt, Ray, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 26/16)
      - Rosenburg, Sam, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 26/17)
      - Schwerin, Burns, Campbell & French, 1995 (Box-folder 26/18)
      - Seattle Joint Port Labor Relations Committee, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 26/19)
      - Vukich and Erickson, 1995, n.d. (Box-folder 26/20)
      - Miscellaneous, 1976-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 26/21-23)
      - Authors Unknown, 1984, 1995, n.d. (Box-folder 26/24)
    - Intra-organizational Memoranda, 1987-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 26/25)
    - Minutes
      - 1978 Negotiations (Box-folder 26/26)
      - Arbitrators' Conference, 1978 (Box-folder 26/27)
      - Coast Labor Relations Committee (LRC), 1976-1997 (Box-folder 26/28-30)
      - Everett Joint LRC, 1977 (Box-folder 26/31)
      - Foremen's Joint LRC, 1979 (Box-folder 26/32)
      - ILWU Coastwide Informal Special Longshore Meeting, 1979 (Box-folder 26/33)
      - ILWU-IBU Organizing Committee, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 26/34)
      - ILWU International Executive Board, 1975-1996 (Box-folder 26/35-36)
      - ILWU Joint Area Labor Relations Committee Columbia River and Oregon Coast Ports, 1976 (Box-folder 26/37)
      - ILWU Joint District Council Meeting, 1987 (Box-folder 26/38)
      - ILWU Joint Oregon-Columbia River Area LRC, 1976, 1979 (Box-folder 26/39)
      - ILWU Local 10 Caucus, 1977 (Box-folder 26/40)
      - ILWU Local 19 Executive Board, 1977-1998 (Box-folder 26/41-45)
      - ILWU Local 19 and ILWU Local 98 LRC Meeting, 1979 (Box-folder 26/46)
      - ILWU Local 19 Membership Meetings, 1976-1998 (Box-folder 26/47 to 27/1-3)
      - ILWU Local 19 Stop Work Meeting, 1978 (Box-folder 27/4)
      - ILWU PGP Workshop, 1976 (Box-folder 27/5)
      - ILWU Puget Sound Area Caucus, 1981 (Box-folder 27/6)
      - ILWU Puget Sound District Council, 1985-1997 (Box-folder 27/7)
      - ILWU Special Tri-Party Executive Board, 1997 (Box-folder 27/8)
      - ILWU Washington Area LRC, 1977-1992 (Box-folder 27/9)
      - ILWU Washington Area Longshore Division LRC, 1997 (Box-folder 27/10)
      - ILWU Welfare and Pension Committee, 1998 (Box-folder 27/11)
      - Joint Accident Prevention Committee, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 27/12)
      - Joint Checker LRC of San Francisco, 1977, 1986 (Box-folder 27/13)
      - King County Labor Council, 1991 (Box-folder 27/14)
      - King County Union Label and Service Trade Council, 1982 (Box-folder 27/15)
      - Lines Joint Port LRC, 1995 (Box-folder 27/16)
      - Longshore LRC of San Francisco, 1994 (Box-folder 27/17)
      - Longshore Joint Port LRC, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 27/18-19)
      - Seattle, Port of, 1976, 1980 (Box-folder 27/20)
      - Seattle Clerks Joint LRC, 1978-1985 (Box-folder 27/21)
      - Seattle Joint Port LRC, 1976-1991 (Box-folder 27/22-26)
      - Seattte Longshore Joint Port LRC, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 27/27)
      - Shop Stewards, 1994 (Box-folder 27/28)
      - Tripartite Joint Port LRC, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 27/29)
    - Agenda
      - PNW Labor Teach-in, 1997 (Box-folder 27/30)
      - Unidentified, n.d. (Box-folder 27/31)
    - Subject Series
      - 87 Contract 'No', 1987 (Box-folder 27/32)
      - APL Beef, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 27/33-35)
      - Arian, Dave, 1994, n.d. (Box-folder 27/36)
      - Australia Waterfront War, 1998 (Box-folder 27/37)
      - Casual Foremen, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 27/38-40)
      - Casual Foremen, 1979 (Box-folder 27/41)
      - Casual Foreman Beef, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 27/42)
      - Centennial, 1986 (Box-folder 27/43)
      - Clerks, 1973-1987, n.d. (Box-folder 27/44-45)
      - Control of Cargo, 1972, 1978 (Box-folder 27/46)
      - Dalzell Data, 1984, 1996 (Box-folder 27/47)
      - D/D Resolutions, 1987-1992, n.d. (Box-folder 27/48)
      - Fortner, Susan, Human Rights Case, 1980, n.d. (Box-folder 27/49)
      - GP 1372, 1981-1997 (Box-folder 27/50-53 to 28/1-6)
      - Grain Contract, 1994 (Box-folder 28/7)
      - Harry Bridges Institute, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 28/8)
      - Hicks Penalty Case, 1979-1981, n.d. (Box-folder 28/9-12)
      - IBT 959 Sealand, 1982 (Box-folder 28/13)
      - ILWU '93 Contract, 1993 (Box-folder 28/14)
      - ILWU Election, 1994 (Box-folder 28/15)
      - Injured Workers, 1983 (Box-folder 28/16)
      - Justice for Janitors, 1988, 1995 (Box-folder 28/17)
      - Korte, Vita, 1983, n.d. (Box-folder 28/18)
      - Lindsay Petition, 1996 (Box-folder 28/19)
      - Linemen, 1968-1978 (Box-folder 28/20)
      - Liverpool, 1995-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 28/21-26)
      - Local 19 Executive Board Information, 1992 (Box-folder 28/27)
      - Logs, 1987 (Box-folder 28/28)
      - McCabe, Paul, Pension File, 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 28/29)
      - Mukono, Rudy, 1980-1981, n.d. (Box-folder 28/30)
      - Nelson, Burt, 1964-1994 (Box-folder 28/31-35)
      - Port, 1975-1979, n.d. (Box-folder 28/36)
      - Puget Sound Regional Organizing Committee, 1993 (Box-folder 28/37)
      - Registration, Mar. 1985, n.d. (Box-folder 28/38)
      - SPD/Pension History, 1953-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 28/39-47)
      - Safety, 1973, 1994 (Box-folder 28/48)